Jean Woodley Bolivard

Full Stack Software Developer



github.com/jwoodleybolivard

jwoodley2000@gmail.com



Santiago, chile

I am a versatile Full Stack Developer with experience in software development, data analysis, and creating comprehensive IT solutions. I excel in web development, data analysis, and data science, as well as possessing strong software programming skills. I leverage my unique combination of skills to drive effective solutions and contribute to the success of organizations, demonstrating a constant commitment to learning and continuous improvement.



EDUCATION

Data Analyst

January 2024 | Google on Coursera



I participated in a data analysis training program supported by Talento Digital, which involved tasks such as data cleaning, analysis, and visualization.

Full Stack Java/JavaScript Developer

August 2023 | Generation Chile/Desafío Latam

Intensive programs focusing on imparting technical competencies in web programming, databases, and software development technologies.

Technical Draftsman

July 2020 | C.E.P.A.H

Instruction in drafting in various areas such as architecture and structures, as well as fostering skills in office applications.



SKILLS

- SQL
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Express
- API | RESTful
- Java
- SringBoot
- Git | GitHub
- R
- Tableau
- PowerBi

- PostgreSQL
- MySQL
- Oracle SQL dev
- GCP
- BigQuery
- handlebars.js
- HTML | CSS
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- Microsoft 365
- Excel

EXPERIENCE

BackOffice Developer

August 2023-Present | Banco Falabella

I extracted and analyzed data from databases using SQL on platforms such as BigQuery in GCP, Sigir, and Cloudera to develop interfaces and regulatory reports for the CMF.

Java Developer

April 2023-August 2023 | Generation Chile

I participated in the web design of the ecommerce site 'Cerveza Huichahue', collaborating with the team in both Front-end and Back-end.

Technical Draftsman

March 2020-January 2022 | Arqu. en tu casa

I have carried out and adapted architectural projects, excelling in time management and critical thinking.



ABILITIES

- Results-oriented and detail-oriented
- Effective time management
- Valued team player
- Effective communication
- Proficient in applying agile methodologies

Certifications:

Data science | PowerBI

Machine Learning | Business Analytics > U. of chile Applied Data Science Project

Languages:

Spanish - Advanced

English - Intermediate

French - Advanced

Creole - Native

